

ABOUT

I am a Front End Web Developer with a positive attitude, open mindset, and a passion for building and designing. With previous experience in the tech field, I have learned to thrive under high pressure environments with firm deadlines. I look forward to opportunities where I can contribute my skills and collaborate with a team to create quality projects.

TECH SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Sass
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Git
- GitHub

- Firebase
- React
- Rest API
- Responsive Design
- Terminal
- Visual Studio Code
- Slack

PROJECTS

ROCKET BATTLE

A two player battle-ship style game. Destroy your opponents rockets before they destroy yours. This project uses JavaScript, JQuery, and the Space X API to return selected stats and data that displays to the user when they have hit a specific rocket in the playing field. This project was made in collaboration with Lucas, Mariya and Alisa.

BREAKING DOWN THE BAD

An informational soundboard generator that plays 3 randomly selected audio files for each character in the Breaking Bad TV series. This app also contains some interesting fun facts about the show, and its characters. This project uses JavaScript, JQuery, React, Firebase, and the Breaking Bad API.



View Portfolio for more awesome projects at

SOCIAL



mxcabrera



mxcabrera



@mxcabreracodes

MIGUEL CABRERA

FRONT END DEVELOPER

migueledward@hotmail.com • (647) 216-0131 • mcabrera.ca

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY | FEB 2020-MAY 2020

Bootcamp Cohort #26 | Web Development Immersive

JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY | AUG 2019-DEC 2019

Part Time Web Development Course | Part Time JavaScript Course

HUMBER COLLEGE | SEPT 2012 - APR 2015

Advanced Diploma with Honours and work placement in Architectural Technology

WORK EXPERIENCE

SCREENING OFFICER

GardaWorld, 2017-Present

- Supervised international security checkpoint
- Assisted customers and resolved all queries related to travel
- Operated detecting devices to screen individuals and prevent passage of prohibited articles into restricted areas

CONTENT CREATION SPECIALIST

Yulio Technologies, 2016-2017

- Created conceptual buildings/environments using SketchUp/Revit
- Debugged projects for errors prior to final release
- Rendered photo-realistic images to create Virtual Reality Scenes

CONTENT CREATION SPECIALIST

KiSP Inc., 2014-2017

- Created net new content for Mobile App KITS Collaborator, using AutoCAD, SketchUp and Revit.
- Edited pre-configured DWG files according to client requests
- Produced renderings of furniture sets from client catalogues